Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Press and publicity, 1914-2010; 1983-2010; Series 13
  - Musical Evening Press Clippings, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - Musical Evening Press Clippings, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - Musical Evening - Press Clippings, 1993; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - Musical Evening Series, 1992; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Brochures - MES FY92, 1992; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Advance Release MES FY92, 1992; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - MES 92 Eroica Trio PSA, 1992; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - Concert Information, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - Book Fair 92, 1992; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Boorstin Review, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Board of Trustees, 1991; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - Echoes of the Past 1992, Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Board List, 1991 September 30; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Trustees, 1991 April 22; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - Board of Trustees '91 Clippings, 1991; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Robin Martin's Articles, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - Board List, 1992 March 20; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Board Overseers of Museum, 1992 March 5; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 76)
  - Board List, 1992 January 29; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - FY92 New Board Members Release, 1992; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - Board of Trustees, 1992 July 7; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - Board of Trustees, 1990 October 18; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - Board of Trustees, 1990; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 81)
  - Board of Trustees PR Committee, 1990; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 82)
  - Past Trustee Lists, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - Corcoran: Trustees, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - Press on David Lloyd Kreeger, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 85)
  - Board of Trustees, Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - Board of Trustee Appointees Press Release, 1993; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - [Photographs], Circa 1990-1994; Series 13 (Box 38, Folder 88)
  - CGA The Sun King, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - The Sun King Transparencies, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Instalation Photos 1972, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Dr. William doing research inn Swedan for Swedan Today Ex. Summer 1967, 1967 August 8; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Dome: Air, Water, Light, Sound SF Museum of Art poster, 1972 August 27; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Language of the Print / The Donald H. Karshan Collection / Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1970 October 25 - 1971 January 3; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Imagination / Photos by Leroy Woodson Jr., Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Gene Davis Recent Paintings, 1950-1960; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Revival! by Eleanor Dickinson, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - New Sculpture Baltimore, Washington, Richmond, 1970 October 10 - November 15; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Contact Prints - Society Exhibition - from openinng preview through Kissinger-Dobrynin visit, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Bierstadt Opening, 1972 April 7; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Wilder new opening, 1971 October 7; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Silhoette Picture of Lumia, 1971 April 12; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Alcston - Altoon - Micton Opening, 1972 May 5; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - The Sunk King, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - The Sunk King Transparencies, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - The Sun King, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Archives: Photos from May 1985 Senior Student Thesis Show in Gallery, 1985 May; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - 38th Biennial: 8x10 B, 1984 October 29; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Gallery Image, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Special Events - Photos Accessioned (Lowell Nesbitt + Al Proom, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Photos of Rental Gallery, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Kathy Koracs Archives, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Susan De Velling class at CSA c. 1900-10, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Work of Edward H. Porthash, N.A. Opening, 1973 March 16; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - [Portraits from 1800s], 1983 September 2; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - President Harding + Philip A De Laszlo in Corcoran Atrium c. 1920, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Education Department Publicity Photos 1970s, Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Photos - Annual Reportt 1969, Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Norman Bluhm Opening March 1969, Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - 360 Jazz Experience April 12, 1969, 1969 April 12; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Leroy Woodson Photography Desk, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Publicity Photos, Contacts + Functions Friends Eve., 1968 September; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Contacts Photos C. Serendipity / Woodson I no. II w/ Photographer John Gossage, 1969 July 15; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Gilliam Krebs, McGowin, 1969 October 3; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Children's Gallery Members, 1969 March; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - David Smith, 1969 October 17; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - McLaughlin Opening, 1968 November 16; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - John Bowden, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Mrs. Inga Hecht / Imagination, DuPont Center, 1968 Decembebrr 12; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Leroy Woodson Jr. Photos / Clayton + Bluhm, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - The Hairy Wher Opening?, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Corcoran Saluters: The Senators, 1969 September 15; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Robert Morris, 1969 November 26; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Berkhowitz Opening, 1969 February 21; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1969 April 25; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous Contacts, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Copies of Soleri Articles, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Liberman Photos, 1959-1969; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Publicity for Various International Exhibitions, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Walkowitz, Abraham Isadora Duncan, 1953-1955; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Lechie Portrait Photos, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Wash '68 New Ptgs: Structure, 1968 September; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Publicity: Robert Morris Photos, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - CGA View of Exterior - 17th Street, Circa 1975-1981; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Lachaise Opening, 1968 October 11; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - David Smith Installation, 1969 October 17 - December 9; Series 13 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - [Press Preview Invite: Changing Reality], Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - [James Drake Press Release], Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Centeservice Shoot FY88, 1988; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Film Shoots - Commercial (w/ fees), Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Film Shoots - Commercial (w/ fees), Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Other Institute Press Releases, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Sample Letter File, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Solicitations, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Suppliers: Printing, Photos, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Printing Information - Press, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Old Media Lists, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Corcoran Publications, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Washington Journalists', Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - 1989 Holiday Open House List, Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Cleveland Museum Press for Homer, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - FY91 Musical Evening Series, 1991; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Press Review Attendance List, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Washingtonian - Where When, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - OGILVY Mather File, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Media Lists, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Invitations, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Record of Phone Messages, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - KSF Correspondence File, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - DBS Correspondence 7/17/89 - 10/10/89, 1989 July 17 - 1989 October 10; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Corporate Spondor Program, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - [Homeless in America], Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - [Art of the New Yorker (1 of 3)], Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - [Art of the New Yorker (2 of 3)], Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - [Art of the New Yorker (3 of 3)], Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - PBS "Odyssey" Broadcast, 1990 December 28; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Corcoran School FDIC Exhibition, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - A New World: Promotion Plan, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - A New World: Press Preview, 1983 December 6; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Copley Acquisition, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Atrium Installation Background Info, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - [Maurice Pendergast Announcement], Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Corcoran Building Project - Forgey Article, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Corcoran Building Project - Brochures, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Building Stats, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Related Articles Building Project, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Corcoran: Archives (PR Contents stored there), Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Storage - Inventory of Special Events Closet, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report File, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Corcoran Friends - Advertising on Metro (empty), Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Mapplethorpe Querries, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Corcoran Schedules Past, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Faxes Sent as of 7/17/89, 1989; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Faxes Sent as of 6/12/90, 1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Extra Photos/Labels, Circa 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - [Press Kit: Odyssey], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - [Press Kit: Spectrum], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - [Spectrum Photos], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - [Press Kit: Homeless in America], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - [Press Kit: A New World], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - [Press Kit: Worthington Whittredge], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - [Press Kit: The Sun King], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - [Press Kit: Niagara], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - [Press Kit: 39th Biennial], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - [Press Kit: Indelible Image], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - [Press Kit: L'Amour Fou], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - [Press Kit: Shaker Designs], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - [Press Kit: Views and Visions], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - [Press Kit: 40th Biennial], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - [Press Kit: Wyeth], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - [Press Kit and Program: American West], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - [Press Kit: Joan Mitchell], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - [Press Kit: Hispanic Art], Circa 1983-1988; Series 13 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - [Press Clips Referencing CGA], 1989 September - 1990 December; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - [Press Clippings Salon Dore Events], 1989-1992; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - [Press Clippings Music Series General], 1990-1992; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - [Press Clippings Jazz Series], 1991; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - [Press Clippings Hauptman, Ott Hannan, Drake, Spector, Kovachevich, Wiley], 1990-1992; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - [Press Clippings Misc/Mentions], 1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - [Press Clippings Misc/Mentions], 1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - [Press Clippings Misc/Mentions], 1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - [Press Clippings Misc/Mentions], 1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - [Press Clippings Past Exhibits], 1989-1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - [Press Clippings Black Folk Perm. Coll.], 1989-1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - [Press Clippings Misc/Mentions], 1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - [Press Clippings Misc/Mentions], 1990; Series 13 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Accordion File of Newspaper Clippings, 1989; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Christina Orr-Cahall, 1989 August 1; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Artist Cancel, 1990; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Boycott / Mapplethorpe, 1989 August 31 - 1990 December; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Mapplethorpe, 1990 January - February 13, 1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Mapplethorpe, 1989 August - September; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Helms, 1989 July - December; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - NEA, 1989 August - December 1991; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - [1989 Brief Reference to CGA (1 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - [1989 Brief Reference to CGA (2 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - [1989 Brief Reference to CGA (1 of 3)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - [1989 Brief Reference to CGA (2 of 3)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - [1989 Brief Reference to CGA (3 of 3)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - [1989 Calendar of Events], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - [1989 Past Exhibitions], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - [1989 Past Students (1 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - [1989 Past Students (2 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - [1989 Permanent Collection (1 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - [1989 Permanent Collection (2 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Japanese, 1989 July - September; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - L. Friedlander, 1989 April 23 - 1990 November 10; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Odyssey, 1988 June - July; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Odyssey, 1989 June - 1991 April; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Terra Sancta, 1990 May - December; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - W. Eggleston, 1990 December; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Arena Stage, 1991 March - April; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Photo, 1988 May - 1991 July; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Berenice Abbott, 1991 July - September; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Photo, 1988 September - 1992 September; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Typologies, 1991 May - December; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - "A Dialogue", 1989 November; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Copley Purchased, 1989 October 18; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Kreeger Exhibition, 1989; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Japanese Photo., 1989 July; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Robert Adams, August 1989; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Kreeger Collection, 1989 September - November; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Lee Miller, 1989 September; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Barye Bronzes, 1989; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - 10+10, 1989 May - August; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Past Exhibitions, 1989 July 23; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Misc., 1988 May - 1991 December; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Misc. / Mention, 1989 September - December; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Misc. / Mention, 1989 December - January 1990; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Misc. / Mention, 1990 January - March; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Lee Miller, 1989 February - April; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - I Dream A World, 1989 January - February; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - I Dream A World, 1989 February - 1990 September; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Sotheby's Deaccessioning, 1988 August - December; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Special Events, 1988 July - May 1989; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1988 July - 1990 September; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Takacs Quartet, 1989 April - June; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Music Series, 1988 December - 1989 April; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Non-Corc Concerts, 1988 October - 1989 May; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Lectures Films, 1988 July - 1989 May; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Paris Trip, 1988 June; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - CGA Staff + Trustees, 1989 May - June; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - CGA Director, 1988 July - 1989 February; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - CGA Current Staff, 1988 July - 1989 April; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - CGA Frank Kelly, 1988 September - 1989 April; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - CGA Ed Nygren, 1988 July - 1989 March; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - CGA Former Staff, 1988 July - 1989 June; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Corcoran Building Project, 1986 December - 1989 February; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Phillip Morris Fundraising Articles, 1988 June - July; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Corcoran Shop, 1988 October - 1989 March; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - [Mapplethorpe and NEA], 1990 February - 1990 May; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - [Mapplethorpe and NEA], 1990 May - 1990 August; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - [Mapplethorpe and NEA], 1990 July - 1991 July; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - [Helms and Mapplethorpe], 1990 January - 1990 October; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - [Mapplethorpe], 1990 January - 1990 February; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - [Mapplethorpe], 1990 January - 1990 March; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - [Mapplethorpe Cincinnati], 1990 April; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - [Mapplethorpe Cincinnati], 1990 April; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - [Mapplethorpe Cincinnati], 1990 April - 1990 July; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - [Mapplethorpe Cincinnati], 1990 May - 1990 October; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - [Mapplethorpe Boston], 1990 July - 1990 October; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - [Mapplethorpe Boston], 1990 October - 1991 August; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - [Mapplethorpe], 1990 July - 1991 September; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - [Mapplethorpe], 1990 August - 1990 November; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - [Mapplethorpe], 1990 November - 1991 March; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - [Mapplethorpe Copies], 1989; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - [Mapplethorpe Copies], 1988-1989; Series 13 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - [Press Misc/Mentions (1 of 2)], 1991 October - 1992 November; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - [Press Misc/Mentions (2 of 2)], 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - [Press: History of the Corcoran, Acquisitions, Music], 1992 February - 1992 October; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - [Press: Cafe and Sightseeing], 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - [Press: Hemicycle (1 of 4)], 1992 January - 1992 March; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - [Press: Hemicycle (2 of 4)], 1992 March - 1992 June; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - [Press: Hemicycle (3 of 4)], 1992 June - 1992 September; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - [Press: Hemicycle (4 of 4)], 1992 September - 1992 November; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - [Press: Corcoran School], 1990; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - [Press: Corcoran School (1 of 2)], 1991 January - 1991 June; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - [Press: Corcoran School (2 of 2)], 1991 June - 1991 December; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - [Press: School Mentions (1 of 3)], 1990 May - 1990 August; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - [Press: School Mentions (2 of 3)], 1990 August - 1990 September; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - [Press: School Mentions (3 of 3)], 1990 September - 1990 November; Series 13 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - [Press: Hispanic, African/Black Exhibits], 1988-1992; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - [Press: Corcoran School of Art], 1988-1989; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - [Press: Permanent Collection], 1992 February - 1992 November; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - [Press: Exhibitions], 1988 June - 1992 November; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - [Press: NEA], 1989-1992; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - [Press: Corcoran School], 1989; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - [Press: Grants, Obituaries, Misc. (1 of 2)], 1989-1992; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - [Press: Grants, Obituaries, Misc. (2 of 2)], 1992 June - 1992 October; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - [Press: Sport in Art, 42nd Biennial], 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - [Press: Typologies, Joesph Renau, Sebastio Salgado, Kutica, Joyce Scott], 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - [Press: Smith Raymond, 10+10, Whittredge, Robert Morris, Tony Cragg], 1989-1992; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - [Press: Winslow Homer], 1990-1991; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - [Press; Rauschenberg], 1990-1991; Series 13 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - [Accordion Folder of Mapplethorpe Clippings], Circa 1989; Series 13 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - [Accordion Folder of Mapplethorpe Clippings], Circa 1989; Series 13 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - [Press: Songs of my People], 1990 May - 1992 February; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - [Press: Songs of my People], 1992 February; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - [Press: Songs of my People], 1992 February - 1992 August; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - [Press: Songs of my People], 1992 August - 1992 October; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - [Press: Songs of my People], 1992 October - 1992 November; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - [Press: Songs of my People], 1992 November - 1992 December; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - [Press: Mentions/Misc.], 1989 March - 1992 February; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - [Press: Mentions/Misc.], 1992 February - 1992 October; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - [Press: Mentions/Misc.], 1992 October - 1993 January; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - [Press: Jazz], 1992 June - 1993 October; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - [Press: Century, Motley, Art Book Fair, Yvonne's Story, Karsh], 1992 December - 1993 April; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - [Press: Folk Art in Latin America, Africa Explores, Gormley, Modern Art, Bellows], 1992; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - [Press: Bierstadt, Wiley, Cadmus, Saldago], 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1991 September - 1992 April; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1992 February - April; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1992 June - August; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, Circa 1988-1992; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Rauschenberg, 1991 December - 1992 October; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Max Weber, 1991 December - 1992 March; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Berlin Exhibit, 1992 May - June 1992; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - "I-con-no-body / I-con-o-graphy", 1992 January - September; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Haring, Warhol Disney, 1992 June - October; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Hiroji Kubota, 1992 June - August; Series 13 (Box 60, Folder 10)